A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1947-1951 FA759
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1950
  - North Carolina, 1950; 02.1950/236
    - North Carolina, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3292)
  - Ohio, 1950; 02.1950/238
    - Ohio, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3292)
  - Ohio - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/238.R
    - Ohio, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3292)
  - Oregon, 1950; 02.1950/240
    - Oregon, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3292)
  - Pennsylvania, 1950; 02.1950/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3293)
  - Pennsylvania - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/241.A
    - Pennsylvania, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3293)
  - Philippines, 1950; 02.1950/242
    - Philippines, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3294)
  - Philippines - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/242.C
    - Philippines, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3294)
  - Philippines - Malaria, 1950; 02.1950/242.I
    - Philippines, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3294)
  - Puerto Rico, 1950; 02.1950/243
  - Puerto Rico - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/243.R
    - Puerto Rico, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3295)
  - Rhode Island, 1950; 02.1950/244
    - Rhode Island, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3295)
  - South Dakota, 1950; 02.1950/247
    - South Dakota, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3295)
  - Tennessee, 1950; 02.1950/248
    - Tennessee, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3295)
  - Virginia, 1950; 02.1950/252
    - Virginia, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3295)
  - Virginia - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/252.R
    - Virginia, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3295)
  - Washington, 1950; 02.1950/253
  - Washington - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/253.R
    - Washington, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3296)
  - Not Used, 02.1950/253.R-492
  - Wisconsin, 1950; 02.1950/255
    - Wisconsin, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3296)
  - South America, 1950; 02.1950/300
    - South America - Administration, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 3297)
    - South America, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3298)
  - South America - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/300.A
    - South America, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3299)
  - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/300.D
    - South America, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3299)
  - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/300.E
    - South America, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3299)
  - South America - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/300.S
    - South America, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3299)
  - Argentina, 1950; 02.1950/301
    - Argentina, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3300)
  - Argentina - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/301.C
    - Argentina, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3300)
  - Argentina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/301.D
    - Argentina, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3300)
  - Bolivia, 1950; 02.1950/303
    - Bolivia, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3300)
  - Bolivia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/303.D
    - Bolivia, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3300)
  - Brazil, 1950; 02.1950/305
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3301)
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3302)
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3303)
  - Brazil - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/305.A
    - Brazil, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3304)
  - Brazil - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/305.C
    - Brazil, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3304)
  - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/305.D
    - Brazil, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3304)
  - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/305.E
    - Brazil, 1950 (Box 493, Folder 3304)
  - Brazil - Malaria, 1950; 02.1950/305.I
    - Brazil, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3305)
  - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1950; 02.1950/305.O
    - Brazil, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3306)
  - Brazil - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/305.R
    - Brazil, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3306)
  - Brazil - Tuberculosis, 1950; 02.1950/305.T
    - Brazil, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3306)
  - Chile, 1950; 02.1950/309
    - Chile, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3307)
  - Chile - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/309.A
    - Chile, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3307)
  - Chile - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/309.C
    - Chile, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3307)
  - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/309.D
    - Chile, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3307)
  - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/309.E
    - Chile, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3307)
  - Colombia, 1950; 02.1950/311
    - Colombia - (A-N), 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3308)
    - Colombia - (O-Z), 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3309)
  - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/311.D
    - Colombia, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3310)
  - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/311.E
    - Colombia, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3310)
  - Costa Rica, 1950; 02.1950/313
    - Costa Rica, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Costa Rica - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/313.C
    - Costa Rica, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Cuba, 1950; 02.1950/315
    - Cuba, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Cuba - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/315.R
    - Cuba, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Ecuador, 1950; 02.1950/317
    - Ecuador, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Guatemala, 1950; 02.1950/319
    - Guatemala, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Guatemala - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/319.D
    - Guatemala, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Guatemala - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/319.R
    - Guatemala, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Haiti, 1950; 02.1950/320
    - Haiti, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Honduras, 1950; 02.1950/321
    - Honduras, 1950 (Box 494, Folder 3311)
  - Mexico, 1950; 02.1950/323
    - Mexico - Administration, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3312)
    - Mexico, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3313)
  - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/323.E
    - Mexico, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3313)
  - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/323.R
    - Mexico, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3313)
  - Nicaragua, 1950; 02.1950/325
    - Nicaragua, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Nicaragua - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/325.D
    - Nicaragua, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Panama, 1950; 02.1950/327
    - Panama, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Panama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/327.E
    - Panama, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Panama - Malaria, 1950; 02.1950/327.I
    - Panama, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Panama - Yellow Fever, 1950; 02.1950/327.O
    - Panama, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Panama - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/327.R
    - Panama, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Peru, 1950; 02.1950/331
    - Peru, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Peru - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/331.A
    - Peru, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Peru - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/331.C
    - Peru, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/331.D
    - Peru, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/331.E
    - Peru, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3314)
  - El Salvador, 1950; 02.1950/333
    - El Salvador, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
  - Dominican Republic, 1950; 02.1950/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
  - Dominican Republic - Malaria, 1950; 02.1950/335.I
    - Dominican Republic, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
  - Uruguay, 1950; 02.1950/337
    - Uruguay, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
  - Uruguay - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/337.A
    - Uruguay, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
  - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/337.E
    - Uruguay, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3315)
  - Venezeula, 1950; 02.1950/339
    - Venezuela, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3316)
  - Venezeula - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/339.E
    - Venezuela, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3317)
  - Venezeula - Yellow Fever, 1950; 02.1950/339.O
    - Venezuela, 1950 (Box 495, Folder 3317)
  - Great Britain, 1950; 02.1950/400
    - Great Britain, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3318)
  - England, 1950; 02.1950/401
    - England - (A-H), 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3318)
  - England - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/401.A
    - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
  - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/401.D
    - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
  - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/401.E
    - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
  - England - Public Health Education, 1950; 02.1950/401.L
    - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
  - England - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/401.R
    - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
  - England - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/401.S
    - England, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3322)
  - Ireland, 1950; 02.1950/403
    - Ireland, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
  - Ireland - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/403.R
    - Ireland, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
  - Scotland, 1950; 02.1950/405
    - Scotland, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
  - Scotland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/405.E
    - Scotland, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
  - Scotland - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/405.S
    - Scotland, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
  - Wales, 1950; 02.1950/407
    - Wales, 1950 (Box 496, Folder 3323)
  - Australia, 1950; 02.1950/410
    - Australia - (A-T), 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3324)
    - Australia - (U-Z), 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
  - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/410.A
    - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
  - Australia - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/410.C
    - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
  - Australia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/410.D
    - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
  - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/410.E
    - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
  - Australia - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/410.R
    - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
  - Australia - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/410.S
    - Australia, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3325)
  - New Zealand, 1950; 02.1950/418
    - New Zealand, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3326)
  - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/418.A
    - New Zealand, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3326)
  - Caribbean, 1950; 02.1950/420
    - Caribbean Region, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3326)
    - Caribbean Region, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3327)
  - Guyana, 1950; 02.1950/423
    - Guiana, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3327)
  - Canada, 1950; 02.1950/427
    - Canada - Administration, 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3328)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3329)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 497, Folder 3330)
    - Canada - University (A-Z), 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3331)
  - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/427.A
    - Canada, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3331)
  - Canada - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/427.C
    - Canada, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3331)
  - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/427.E
    - Canada, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3331)
  - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/427.R
    - Canada, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3332)
  - Canada - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/427.S
    - Canada, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3332)
  - Jamaica, 1950; 02.1950/437
    - Jamaica, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - Jamaica - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/437.A
    - Jamaica, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - Jamaica - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/437.E
    - Jamaica, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - Trinidad, 1950; 02.1950/451
    - Trinidad, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - Sri Lanka, 1950; 02.1950/462
    - Sri Lanka, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - Sri Lanka - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/462.C
    - Sri Lanka, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - Sri Lanka - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/462.E
    - Sri Lanka, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - Sri Lanka - Malaria, 1950; 02.1950/462.I
    - Sri Lanka, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - Hong Kong, 1950; 02.1950/463
    - Hong Kong, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3333)
  - India, 1950; 02.1950/464
    - India - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3334)
    - India - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3335)
  - India - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/464.A
    - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
  - India - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/464.C
    - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
  - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/464.E
    - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
  - India - Malaria, 1950; 02.1950/464.I
    - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
  - India - Public Health Demonstrations, 1950; 02.1950/464.J
    - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
  - India - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/464.R
    - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
  - India - Social Services, 1950; 02.1950/464.S
    - India, 1950 (Box 498, Folder 3336)
  - Pakistan, 1950; 02.1950/465
    - Pakistan, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Pakistan - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/465.C
    - Pakistan, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Pakistan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/465.E
    - Pakistan, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Pakistan - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/465.S
    - Pakistan, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Burma, 1950; 02.1950/468
    - Burma, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Iraq, 1950; 02.1950/470
    - Iraq, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Iraq - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/470.C
    - Iraq, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Iraq - Malaria, 1950; 02.1950/470.I
    - Iraq, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - New Guinea, 1950; 02.1950/472
    - New Guinea, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Malayasia, 1950; 02.1950/473
    - Malaysia, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Malayasia - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/473.A
    - Malaysia, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3337)
  - Africa, 1950; 02.1950/475
    - Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
  - Africa - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/475.A
    - Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
    - MOR-1 Morison, Robert S. "Diary of a Trip to Syria and Africa", 1950 (Box 563, Folder 3838)
  - Africa - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/475.S
    - Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
  - East Africa Region, 1950; 02.1950/477
    - East Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
  - East Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/477.A
    - East Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
  - East Africa Region - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/477.C
    - East Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
  - East Africa Region - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/477.E
    - East Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3338)
  - Egypt, 1950; 02.1950/485
    - Egypt - Administration, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3339)
    - Egypt, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3340)
  - Egypt - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/485.A
    - Egypt, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3340)
  - Egypt - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/485.C
    - Egypt, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3340)
  - Egypt - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/485.E
    - Egypt, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3340)
  - Egypt - Public Health Demonstrations, 1950; 02.1950/485.J
    - Egypt, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3340)
  - South Africa, 1950; 02.1950/487
    - South Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3341)
  - South Africa - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/487.A
  - South Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3342)
  - South Africa - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/487.C
    - South Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3342)
  - South Africa - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/487.E
    - South Africa, 1950 (Box 499, Folder 3342)
  - West Africa, 1950; 02.1950/495
    - West Africa, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3343)
  - West Africa - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/495.A
    - West Africa, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3343)
  - France, 1950; 02.1950/500
    - France - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3344)
    - France - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3345)
    - France - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3346)
  - France - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/500.A
    - France, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
  - France - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/500.D
    - France, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
  - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/500.E
    - France, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
  - France - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/500.R
    - France, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
  - France - Social Services, 1950; 02.1950/500.S
    - France, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
  - Corsica, 1950; 02.1950/502
  - Corsica - Malaria, 1950; 02.1950/502.I
    - Corsica, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
  - Vietnam, 1950; 02.1950/509
    - Vietnam, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
  - Asia, 1950; 02.1950/600
    - Asia, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
  - Asia - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/600.S
    - Asia, 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3347)
    - Asia - Evans, Roger F. - Diary South and Southeast Asia, September-December 1950 (Box 500, Folder 3348)
  - China, 1950; 02.1950/601
    - China, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3349)
  - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/601.E
    - China, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3349)
  - China - Social Services, 1950; 02.1950/601.S
    - China, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3349)
  - Taiwan, 1950; 02.1950/605
    - Taiwan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3350)
  - Taiwan - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/605.A
    - Taiwan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3350)
  - Taiwan - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/605.C
    - Taiwan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3350)
  - Japan, 1950; 02.1950/609
    - Japan - Administration - (A-Ins), 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3351)
    - Japan - International Christian - University, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3352)
    - Japan - (Int-Oz), 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3353)
    - Japan - (P-Z), 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3354)
  - Japan - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/609.A
    - Japan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3355)
  - Japan - Nursing, 1950; 02.1950/609.C
    - Japan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3355)
  - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/609.E
    - Japan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3355)
  - Japan - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/609.R
    - Japan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3355)
  - Japan - Social Services, 1950; 02.1950/609.S
    - Japan, 1950 (Box 501, Folder 3355)
  - Korea, 1950; 02.1950/613
  - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/613.E
    - Korea, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3357)
    - Korea, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3357)
  - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/613.R
    - Korea, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3357)
  - Thailand, 1950; 02.1950/617
    - Thailand, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3356)
  - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/617.A
    - Thailand, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3356)
  - Thailand - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/617.R
    - Thailand, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3356)
  - Southeast Asia, 1950; 02.1950/625
    - Southeast Asia, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3356)
  - Holland, 1950; 02.1950/650
    - Netherlands, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3358)
  - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/650.E
    - Netherlands, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
  - Holland - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/650.R
    - Netherlands, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
  - Holland - Social Services, 1950; 02.1950/650.S
    - Netherlands, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
  - Indonesia, 1950; 02.1950/652
    - Indonesia, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
  - Indonesia - Medical Services, 1950; 02.1950/652.A
    - Indonesia, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
  - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/652.E
    - Indonesia, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
  - Indonesia - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/652.R
    - Indonesia, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
  - Java, 1950; 02.1950/655
    - Java, 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3359)
  - Europe, 1950; 02.1950/700
    - Europe - Struthers, Robert R., 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3360)
  - Europe - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/700.A
    - Europe - Bachmeyer, Arthur C. - "Survey of European Medical Schools", 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3361)
  - Europe - Social Services, 1950; 02.1950/700.S
    - Europe - Buchanan, Norman S. - "Marginalia on European Program", 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3361)
    - Europe - Mosely, Philip E. - "European Trip Notes", 1950 (Box 502, Folder 3362)
  - Austria, 1950; 02.1950/705
    - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
  - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/705.A
    - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
  - Austria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/705.D
    - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
  - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/705.E
    - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
  - Austria - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/705.R
    - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
  - Austria - Social Services, 1950; 02.1950/705.S
    - Austria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3363)
  - Belgium, 1950; 02.1950/707
    - Belgium, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3364)
  - Belgium - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/707.A
    - Belgium, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3364)
  - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/707.E
    - Belgium, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3364)
  - Belgium - Social Services, 1950; 02.1950/707.S
    - Belgium, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3364)
  - Yugoslavia, 1950; 02.1950/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3365)
  - Yugoslavia - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/710.A
    - Yugoslavia, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3365)
  - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/710.E
    - Yugoslavia, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3365)
  - Bulgaria, 1950; 02.1950/711
    - Bulgaria, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3365)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1950; 02.1950/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3365)
  - Denmark, 1950; 02.1950/713
    - Denmark, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
  - Denmark - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/713.D
    - Denmark, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
  - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/713.E
    - Denmark, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
  - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/713.R
    - Denmark, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
  - Iceland, 1950; 02.1950/715
    - Iceland, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
  - Scandinavia, 1950; 02.1950/716
    - Scandinavia, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3366)
  - Germany, 1950; 02.1950/717
    - Germany, 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3367)
    - Germany - (A-U), 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3368)
    - Germany - (A-U), 1950 (Box 503, Folder 3369)
    - Germany - University - (A-Z), 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3370)
    - Germany - (V-Z), 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
  - Germany - Medical Services, 1950; 02.1950/717.A
    - Germany, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
  - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/717.D
    - Germany, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
  - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/717.E
    - Germany, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
  - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/717.R
    - Germany, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
  - Germany - Social Services, 1950; 02.1950/717.S
    - Germany, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3371)
  - Angaur Island, 1950; 02.1950/741
    - Angaur Island, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3372)
  - Greece, 1950; 02.1950/749
    - Greece, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3372)
  - Greece - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/749.E
    - Greece, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3372)
  - Greece - Humanities and Arts, 1950; 02.1950/749.R
    - Greece, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3372)
  - Hungary, 1950; 02.1950/750
    - Hungary, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3372)
  - Italy, 1950; 02.1950/751
    - Italy, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3373)
  - Italy - Medical Services, 1950; 02.1950/751.A
    - Italy, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3374)
  - Italy - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1950; 02.1950/751.D
    - Italy, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3374)
  - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/751.E
    - Italy, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3374)
  - Italy - Social Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/751.S
    - Italy, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3374)
  - Luxembourg, 1950; 02.1950/760
    - Luxembourg, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3374)
  - Norway, 1950; 02.1950/767
    - Norway, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3375)
  - Norway - Medical Sciences, 1950; 02.1950/767.A
    - Norway, 1950 (Box 504, Folder 3375)
  - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1950; 02.1950/767.E